[
    {
      "id": 0,
      "question": "Santa saw someone reading the _____ translation, and then put him on the naughty list.",
      "answer": "passion",
      "answer1": "Passion",
      "answer2": "mormon",
      "answer3": "Mormon"
     
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What is Mrs.Claus real name?",
      "answer": "albina",
      "answer1": "Albina",
      "answer2": "Wife",
      "answer3": "wife"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "How much kids does santa have???",
      "answer": "two",
      "answer1": "2",
      "answer2": "Two",
      "answer3": "2"

    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Whats Santas favorite food?",
        "answer": "cookie",
        "answer1": "Cookie",
        "answer2": "Bible",
        "answer3": "bible"
       
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is Santas foot Size?",
        "answer": "11",
        "answer1": "Eleven",
        "answer2": "eleven",
        "answer3": "11"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "How much reindeers does Santa Have?",
        "answer": "ten",
        "answer1": "Ten",
        "answer2": "10",
        "answer3": "10"
  
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is Santas favorite drink?",
        "answer": "milk",
        "answer1": "Milk",
        "answer2": "pepsi",
        "answer3": "Pepsi"
       
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "How old was Santa before he stopped aging?",
        "answer": "thirthy three",
        "answer1": "Thirty three",
        "answer2": "33",
        "answer3": "ThirtyThree"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How much kids does Santa want",
        "answer": "4",
        "answer1": "four",
        "answer2": "Four",
        "answer3": "4"
  
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Does Santa consider i68 worthy of his presents?",
        "answer": "maybe",
        "answer1": "no",
        "answer2": "No",
        "answer3": "Maybe"
       
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "There are Elfs that sing in santas Choir, can you guess one of them?",
        "answer": "tanya",
        "answer1": "Anzhelika",
        "answer2": "Tanya",
        "answer3": "anzhelika"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "this is the end",
        "answer": "",
        "answer1": "",
        "answer2": "",
        "answer3": ""
      }







  ]
  